I'm in Vienna today, we're doing the webshop pictures.
I'm here with Julia, she's definitely from paradise.
It's an exciting day.
And my au pair, yay!
Who do you dream of? Who are you hiding from?
We saw some previews and they were absolutely amazing.
Selina rocks the pants and it looks perfect.
We're done taking the pictures in the studio.
We'll go outdoors in a sec, but I have to go in there and look at everything.
Already spoken
All of my dreams are lying shattered and broken
I was trying to breathe
In your house of cards
I was trying to leave
I'm so excited!
Oh my fingers are freezing!
My face is freezing!
The wind is blowing hard.
Yeah, it's very warm.
Twist the knife
When you make me cry
All of my words are now already spoken
All of my dreams are lying shattered and broken
I was dying to breathe
In your house of cards
I was dying to live
We had a wonderful day in Vienna. Thanks so much for inviting me.
Thank you for coming. We drove a lot of roller coasters and now
one last ride and then I'll go home. Thanks again
and see you!